[
    {
        "id": 1035,
        "question": "Which of the following commands will install Ansible on Ubuntu?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "sudo apt install ansible",
            "answer_b": "sudo apt install ansible-controller",
            "answer_c": "sudo apt install ansible-master",
            "answer_d": "sudo apt install ansible-server",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "DevOps"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 914,
        "question": "The Kubernetes Network proxy runs on which node?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Master Node",
            "answer_b": "Worker Node",
            "answer_c": "All the nodes",
            "answer_d": "None of the mentioned",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 899,
        "question": "Kubernetes uses _____________ to connect to ouath 2 providers to offload the authentication to external services.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Webhook Token Authentication",
            "answer_b": "Keystone Password",
            "answer_c": "OpenID Connect Tokens",
            "answer_d": "Authentication Proxy",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 903,
        "question": "The command to create Kubernetes service is",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "kubectl expose",
            "answer_b": "kubectl deploy",
            "answer_c": "kubectl run",
            "answer_d": "kubectl set service",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 1054,
        "question": "Which command would you use to gather facts with Ansible?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "ansible your_server -m gather",
            "answer_b": "ansible your_server -m setup",
            "answer_c": "ansible your_server -m info",
            "answer_d": "ansible your_server -m fact",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "DevOps"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 964,
        "question": "What is a kube-proxy used for?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "To supplant an authentic webpage in a search engine's index and search page results",
            "answer_b": "To load-balance traffic that is destined for services to the correct backend pods",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 1047,
        "question": "Which Ansible command will you use to install Apache on Ubuntu host?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "ansible your_host_name_here -b -m apt -a \"name=apache2 state=latest\"",
            "answer_b": "ansible your_host_name_here -b -m yum -a \"name=apache2 state=latest\"",
            "answer_c": "ansible your_host_name_here -b -m wget -a \"name=apache2 state=latest\"",
            "answer_d": "ansible your_host_name_here apt install \"name=apache2 state=latest\"",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "DevOps"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 959,
        "question": "What can you deploy on Kubernetes?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Containers",
            "answer_b": "Virtual machines",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 1049,
        "question": "Which command will you use to run a playbook called install.yaml with Ansible?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "ansible-playbook install.yml",
            "answer_b": "ansible install.yml",
            "answer_c": "ansible --playbook install.yml",
            "answer_d": "ansible -p install.yml",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "DevOps"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 1043,
        "question": "What are Ansible ad-hoc commands?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Ansible ad-hoc commands are commands which helps you execute simple tasks without the need of creating playbooks",
            "answer_b": "Ansible ad-hoc commands are also known as Ansible playbooks",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "DevOps"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }
]
